{
    "id": "d84bbaca542048959a8ec66cefbb4fa1",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He asked me …………………. I would like to accompany him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "James ran very fast ………………….. he could not catch up with Mike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "yet",
                "still",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Two ……………….. two make four.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "also",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I work hard ………………. I may pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "and",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you work hard, you will pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whether",
                "If",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is older ………………… her husband.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They left the town …………………. the epidemic had spread there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "while",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Go ………………. you like.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "where",
                "whence"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither a borrower ........................ a lender be.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nor",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Look ...................... you leap.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "while",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me ..................... I wanted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been a long time ......................... I last met him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... you focus on your work, you will not succeed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We eat ........................... we may live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "what",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}